

Mykola Kolomoyets

Front-End React Developer

Details

Lviv, Ukraine +38 067 659 77 96 mykola.kolomoiets@gmail.com github repositories ₽

Skills

HTML/(S)CSS

MaterialUI/TailwindCSS

JavaScript (ES6)

Typescript

React.js

Redux (Toolkit incl. RTKQuery)

React Native

Git

REST API

Next.js

Testing

English: B2

Profile

Young, self-learned web-developer with more then 3 years of self-learning by creating SPA-s for range of topics and more then 2 year of commercial experiance with creating and implementing Fin-tech and blockchain platforms from scratch. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in team setting. Experienced with latest cutting edge development tools and procedures

Employment History

React Front-End developer, Appexoft, Lviv

January 2022 - Present

Managed to create the front-end architecture of Fin-Tech webapplications including blochchain platforms with reliable REST API connection and implementing of all of it.

Covered the project with unit test for core-functionality

Made code review

Junior Front-End developer, 42flows.tech, Lviv

January 2021- January 2022

Created and supported single-page web-applications for social media chatbots for Financial Institutions such as: Universal Bank, Alfa Bank and X5 Group

Trainee Front-End developer, Chatbots.studio_>, Lviv

June 2020 - January 2021

Passed the internship with creating single-page web-applications for social media chatbots for Financial Institutions

Education

Bachelor, Lviv Polytechnic National University

September 2018 - July 2022

Graduated with high honors at Computer Science spiciality.

Main topics to learn were: Typography, Web-Design and Web-development

Soft Skills

Self-discipline, decision-making, time-management, teamwork, problem-solving, Agile/Scrum/Kanban, adaptability, openness to criticism, creativity, practise in expressing opinions.

Courses

React: The Complete Guide (Hooks, Routing, Redux), Udemy August 2020 - February 2022

Typescript 2022 Edition, Udemy

Jule 2021 - January 2022

React Native: The Practical Guide 2022, Udemy

February 2022 - July 2022